{
    "subject": "resource/Jimmy_Wales",
    "predicate": "ontology/board",
    "object": "resource/MIT_Center_for_Collective_Intelligence",
    "human_readable": "Jimmy Wales serves on the board of MIT Center for Collective Intelligence.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9850436449050903,
            "question": "What type of role does Jimmy Wales have at the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.974614679813385,
            "question": "What could be some of Jimmy Wales's contributions to the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115051031112671,
            "question": "Who serves on the board of MIT Center for Collective Intelligence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6268854141235352,
            "question": "What is the purpose of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6112854480743408,
            "question": "What field does the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.608128011226654,
            "question": "Name an institution that Jimmy Wales is connected to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5570831298828125,
            "question": "What organization is Jimmy Wales affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5425145030021667,
            "question": "Is Jimmy Wales involved in academia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.324863076210022,
            "question": "Does Jimmy Wales have a connection with Massachusetts Institute of Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23970286548137665,
            "question": "What does it mean to serve on a board?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jimmy Wales serves on the board of MIT Center for Collective Intelligence.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7010_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Jimmy Wales have a connection with Massachusetts Institute of Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7010_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jimmy Wales involved in academia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7010_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What organization is Jimmy Wales affiliated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7010_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7010_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context information, Jimmy Wales is indeed a member of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Jimmy Wales is a member of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence. While \"serves on the board\" might imply formal board membership, his membership in the center can be considered as serving a similar role, thus supporting the statement that Jimmy Wales serves on the board of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}